[
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following views can be used to write on multiple tables?",
      "opt1": "Database view",
      "opt2": "Projection view",
      "opt3": "Maintenance view",
      "opt4": "Help view",
      "correctAns": "Maintenance view",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many tables draw a projection view?",
      "opt1": "1",
      "opt2": "2",
      "opt3": "3",
      "correctAns": "1",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is true.",
      "opt1": "A view contains data",
      "opt2": "Views can be buffered",
      "opt3": "Views cannot be buffered",
      "opt4": "None of above",
      "correctAns": "Views cannot be buffered",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "One of the disadvantages of CDS views is that it cannot be reused.",
      "opt1": "True",
      "opt2": "False",
      "correctAns": "False",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following is a conditional expression in CDS view?",
      "opt1": "CASE",
      "opt2": "IF",
      "opt3": "FOR",
      "correctAns": "CASE",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which view types can you use to join two tables with an outer join?",
      "opt1": "Maintenance view",
      "opt2": "Database view",
      "opt3": "Projection view",
      "opt4": "Help view",
      "correctAns": "Maintenance view",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "You define a database view A and a maintenance view B in the ABAP dictionary. What restrictions apply to these views?",
      "opt1": "Only B can have either a left outer join or an inner join.",
      "opt2": "The tables joined in B must have foreign key relationships.",
      "opt3": "Only A can be used in the FROM clause of a SELECT statement.",
      "opt4": "The tables joined in A must have foreign key relationships",
      "correctAns": "The tables joined in B must have foreign key relationships.",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "What type of ABAP Dictionary view is implemented as an “INNER JOIN”?",
      "opt1": "Maintenance View",
      "opt2": "Help View",
      "opt3": "Database View",
      "opt4": "Projection View",
      "correctAns": "Database View",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "What does a view do?",
      "opt1": "Contains other views",
      "opt2": "Can be contained in a window",
      "opt3": "Contains a view controller",
      "opt4": "Contains windows",
      "opt5": "If entered by an inbound plug, can cause an event handler method to be called",
      "correctAns": "Contains other views",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "Difference between projection view and database view.",
      "opt1": "Projection view can be created using one or more table and database view be created using single table",
      "opt2": "Projection view be created using a single table and database view can be created using one or more table",
      "opt3": "None of the above",
      "correctAns": "Projection view be created using a single table and database view can be created using one or more table",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is true about views? More than one answer is correct.",
      "opt1": "A view is automatically created on the database upon activation",
      "opt2": "A view contains data",
      "opt3": "Maintenance Views are not updateable",
      "opt4": "Views can be buffered",
      "correctAns": ["A view is automatically created on the database upon activation", "Maintenance Views are not updateable"],
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "The ____ type of ABAP Dictionary view consists of one or more transparent tables and may be accessed by an ABAP program using Open SQL.",
      "opt1": "Database view",
      "opt2": "Projection view",
      "opt3": "Help view",
      "opt4": "Entity view",
      "correctAns": "Database view",
      "resource": "https://help.sap.com/viewer/cb890f38e48f4b6090987452ea9e9d0a/1909.000/en-US/6e5f6c13eb9c4cdd88e540697ca87e8f.html",
      "proposedAns": ""
    }
  ]
  